Travis Hanneman

thanneman1@gmail.com Scottsdale, AZ

Full-stack Developer

github.com/thanneman linkedin.com/in/thanneman thanneman.com

Summary

I'm a Full Stack Developer and recent graduate from the Software Engineering program at Thinkful. Experience with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, jQuery, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Git, RESTful APIs, data structure, and computer algorithms. I'm a strong media and communication professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Design Studies from Arizona State University.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, jQuery, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Git, RESTful APIs, Data Structure, Computer Algorithms, Scrum, Agile, and Web Applications

Recent Projects

WatchThisWhere | GitHub | Live

- Find where to stream your favorite movies and tv shows with WatchThisWhere.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React.js

One-Liner | GitHub | Live

- A comical community to post and rate the best jokes.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Mocha, Chai

Discscore | GitHub | Live

- Quickly track your disc golf games, scores, and locations.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Mocha, Chai

Movie Info | GitHub | Live

- Want to know more about your favorite movie? Use the Movie Info app to search for movies to find the cast, trailers, recommendations, and more.
- Tech: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, and Fetch API

Experience

Deluxe Corporation

Web Services Specialist

Oct 2018 - Current

Remote

- Build/manage storefronts for clients. Including: add/remove products, update HTML/CSS branding, building/update templates for customizable products.
- Provide support, management, and development of company web technology & application services.
- Collaborate with the development team on any bugs, client requests, and product builds.

Chive Media Group

Austin, TX

Nov 2014 - Oct 2018

Managed a team of 13 employees of the editorial team for the CHIVE.com.

- Reported insights and Key Performance Indicators to the C-level executives for editorial and social media departments.
- Integrated with both the Sales and Product departments to effectively implement new ideas, solutions, and procedures to promote growth.

Education

Thinkful **Computer Software Engineering**

Manager, Editorial Operations

Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

• Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards with a focus on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, jQuery, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Mocha, Chai, Git, RESTful APIs, algorithms, and data structures.

Arizona State University